Name: Chiam Zong Ngee

Email: 21008914@myrp.edu.sg

Mobile: +65 88746209

Internship Objective

I am a hardworking student who is always ready to learn anything new in life and improve in any areas I am lacking I believe that I can fit in your company as I have the relevant skills that I learned in school. I am excited to apply my skillsets to make beneficial contributions. I hope to gain more experience in the tech industry.

Summary of Key Skills

- Programming using Python; Java; HTML; C#
- Database Systems
- Internetworking Security
- Android app development
- Adobe Photoshop; Adobe Illustrator; Adobe XD
- Problem-solving
- Teamwork
- Interpersonal communications
- Creative thinking

Education

Republic Polytechnic 2021 – Current Diploma in Design and Development Anticipated completion date: May 2024

Riverside Secondary School

N'Level, O'Level 2015 – 2020

Boonlay/Qihua Primary School 2009 – 2014

PSLE

Work Experience

SuperPets Sales Assistant

1/01/2019 - 1/02/2019

• Assist with customer's needs, restocking products, Help transport purchases to transportation, help to pack items for delivery.

MCI

Event Helper

- Secure jewellery from popup stores
- Transfer jewellery to the security truck

RecruitPedia Warehouse Event

- Picking and packing gym products
- Stacking box orders

•

Volunteer and Leadership Experience

Riverside Secondary School

January 2015 – December 2020

Volunteer

• Yearly R3 day where I collect recyclable items for the whole day.

Boys Brigade

January 2015 - December 2020

Sergeant

- Train juniors with leg work
- Coordinate members to attend other activities like Christian education.
- Volunteer at Old folks home once a year

Students' Overseas Trip to Hong Kong

10 November 2018 – 17 November 2018

References

Available upon request

- End –